## Nick Wesselmann

<u>Nick.Wesselmann@Mystic5523.com</u> | (913)579-7592 | Mission, KS <u>Linkedin.com/in/nick-wesselmann</u> | <u>Github.com/Mystic5523</u> | Website: <u>www.Mystic5523.com</u>

### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Webdesigner with background in security. 12 years of experience in interacting with people, both in person and remotely. Duties include building and using databases to track information and running the switchboard for a national mutual fund company. Graduated from a Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, GIT, Github, Firebase, Bootstrap, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, Command Line, MS Word and Excel.

## **PROJECTS**

- Uses multiple APIs to search for a recipe and uses the results to find a video
- Utilizes Bootstrap, Bootswatch, and some custom CSS for styles
- Utilizes the YouTube API for an embedded iFrame player.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Security Officer Aug 2006 - Present

Allied Universal Security Services

- Level 5 Master Security Officer
- CPR/AED Certified
- First Aid Certified
- Management of Aggressive Behavior (MOAB Self Defence) Certified

Nutrition Services 2001 - Aug 2006

Shawnee Mission Medical Center

- Prepare and served meals to patients and employees
- Sanitation Duties

## **Volunteer Work**

*Camp Companion* 2002 - 2009

Camp Quality Northwest Missouri

- Supervise and Monitor children of all ages
- Set up and take down camp equipment

## **EDUCATION**

# University of Kansas

Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp

- HTML5
- CSS
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- Firebase
- Node Js
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Express
- Handlebars JS
- React Js.

## Johnson County Community College

Associates of Arts in Criminal Justice

- Criminology
- Vice President of Lambda Alpha Epsilon Criminal Justice Fraternity